Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them with
you, our love's so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We don't even want to do it.
Tony's acting as a decoy?
Don't worry, he'll be fine.
He's buying us some time.
But we've got to hurry!
Take me to Luffy and the others.
Sure, but Sanji, I thought
you got shot earlier?
Hello?
We've got him, sir.
And don't worry, he
won't be going anywhere?
So where are you?
Speak up I'm at the front of the big
casino with the alligator on top.
And rain base, rain dinners?
Nice job.
That was such a convincing performance
that your boss is on the way.
You should really consider
a career in acting.
Really?
Gee, thanks!
Hey, um, you're gonna
let me go now, right?
No, sir.
Yeah, I didn't think so.
More of those millions creeps
are checking out our handiwork.
You better get going.
You know what to do, Chopper?
Who are you supposed to be?
My name is Mr. Prince.
Did you see who did this to our friends?
Hey, wait a minute.
Was it you?
Did you take them down?
Whatever I can manage.
Yes, I did it!
It was me, Mr. Prince!
My name's Mr.
Prince, you are Mr. Prince!
What the hell?
A guy.
He was called Mr. Prince.
I see.
The bridge collapsed!
The bridge to the casino just collapsed!
That's how Chopper and
I did it, more or less.
But is Tony going to be alright?
Yeah, that little furball's
got a few tricks up his sleeve.
You bastard.
I know you're here somewhere, Mr. Prince.
When I find you, I'm going
to introduce you to my hook.
Please don't notice me.
All of us are going to die!
The water's going to be
up to our next minute!
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, you stupid Katorea!
If you're hungry, come and get me!
Are you nuts, Nami?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to lure that Katorea in close
enough so he'll bite this cage apart!
Hey!
That's not a bad idea!
Yeah, come and get us, you stupid banana!
You rotten banana!
Look, I told you, that
thing's not a banana.
It's an alligator with a
banana growing out of its head.
But it's called a banana Katorea.
Let me explain it to you.
You've heard of the monkey dance, right?
You don't banana!
Shut up and listen for a second!
Okay, look, there's a dance called
the monkey dance, you follow?
Even though it's got the word monkey
in it, it isn't an actual monkey.
Don't touch those bars!
How do you know they're not
bananas if you haven't eaten one?
Watch out!
It's just too tough!
The banana didn't even ditch it!
Vivi, please, hurry!
Hey, Straw Hats.
We're all about to die!
How can you just sit there like that?
You should be trying to
get us out of here, too!
Tell me something.
How much do you guys know?
What exactly is Crocodile after?
The woman at Crocodile's side.
Did you know the world governments had a
sizable price on her head for 20 years?
As I recall, over 70 million berries.
70 million?
Holy Mellow!
But why is it so much?
It's almost as much as Crocodile had.
The moment those two joined forces,
this insurrection became
more than just a simple coup.
If they're not stopped here and now,
this could very well turn into something
the whole world would get dragged into.
The whole world?
Wait, what do you mean?
This is starting to sound
a little far-fetched.
I don't care if all that is true.
Huh, I don't need any other excuses.
I'm still gonna kick that guy's ass.
I See so how do you
intend to get out of here?
Wait just tough it out.
He says she brings some help back
Vivi, I know you're doing all
you can, but please hurry back.
Dammit, if only my swordsmanship were
better, I could cut through this stupid cage.
We'd be free.
It's really impolite to make a lot of
noise at mealtime like you were doing.
I'll teach you how to behave.
Bad manner, kick course!
Hey guys, been waiting long?
Jay, it's Mr. Prince!
We're finally gonna get out of here now!
Thank you.
Well, don't just stand there!
Find the key and get us out of here!
Mommy, my dear!
Do you love me now?
Oh, well...
Um, sure!
And I'll love you even more if
you hurry up and open this cage!
He is one lovesick idiot.
Phoebe!
All right, way to go!
More diners with bad manners, huh?
Get them, Saucy!
Smash those weird bananas into pudding!
Don't worry, I'm gonna teach these
bananas some proper table manners alright.
Since theirs are so bad they attacked
a lady, I'll do it the hard way.
I'll take my sweet time doing it
too, cause nobody does that to Nami.
We don't have any time for chivalry!
One second strikes!
No, make that one instant strikes!
The third one who just
came in has the key.
Hey, how do you know that, Smokey?
Guess your ears aren't
as big as your mouth.
Isn't that one's growl the same
as the one who swallowed the key?
Smart thinking collapsing the
bridge to buy time like that.
There are obviously more straw
hats here than we thought.
So that was all done to lure us away
so they could rescue their friends.
Of course it was. Hey!
Key!
There it is! Get it!
Hey, wait a minute!
That doesn't look like the key.
What's wrong?
What the?
Yes, water at last.
It's a miracle!
Hey, it's him.
Mr. Three!
Mr. Three?
What was he doing in the
belly of a banana Katorea?
I thought I was a goner stupid
crocodile so you thought
you could get rid of me but
you didn't try hard enough
the moment I was swallowed
I used the last of my power
to create that waxwax ball
that was how I survived a key
Wait, why do they want
this key so bad? Hold on.
A room that's surrounded
by and flooding with water.
A cage full of Straw Hats.
And they're screaming
like mad for this key.
Now I see what's happening here.
Mr.
Three, I presume. Ah!
How'd you know who I was?
Well, your hairstyle gave it away.
I'll take the key.
Toss it here.
Hmm?
Sure thing! Here you go!
Hey!
I don't know who you are,
but if you want the Straw Hats
out, you're no friend of mine.
You want the key?
Go find it! Good luck!
You'll need it with all
those alligators around.
Trust me, I know.
Jerk.
So what happens if
their rescuer is able to
ascertain which banana
Katorea swallowed the key?
Huh, well, even if they were able to get
the key, it wouldn't make any difference.
I've had the real one with me.
The key in the gator's belly's a fraud,
but that's for me to know
and them to find out.
You're bad.
Wait a minute, Sanji.
He might be good for something, like
using those wax powers to make a key.
You're right.
Nice work, Candleman.
Now there are just two more things to do.
Let's go.
We have to hurry.
Right.
We've got to stop the rebels
before they attack Alubarna.
We should be able to get
out through that hallway.
There's a problem with that.
Namely, dozens of banana-gators.
That's it!
I can take on hundreds
of those weird bananas!
Um, that problem solved.
And I had so much trouble
with just one of them.
No, don't be so hard on yourself.
Those two just have
crazy abnormal strength.
Yeah?
I'd be even stronger if I
wasn't soaked right now!
Ah!
This place is falling apart!
Yeah, we can see that!
Oh no!
The passageway's probably due!
We've got to get out of here right now!
All right,
Straw Hats time to pay if
the banana gators haven't
finished you off yet You'll
wish they had by the time.
I'm done with you
This can't be
Hey, you alive there, Luffy?
Usopp, please wake up!
Come on, just kick your legs or something!
Hey, help us pull you out of here!
Geez, why would a pirate want devil
fruit powers if it means he can't swim?
What? Smoker!
Hey, Zoro, what are you doing?
In case you forgot, that guy's our enemy!
Back off!
I didn't want to do it, but he
was about to die, that's all.
Whatever.
We gotta get moving, guys.
We've lost too much time already.
Vivi, can we still make it?
I don't know.
Hey, Nami.
You still have that perfume I bought you?
Huh? Yeah. But why?
Put some of it on, please.
Okay.
Oh, just one whiff of it makes me
swoon like a schoolboy in love.
I did not to mention make
you act like an idiot.
Why did you save my life?
Zoro, quick!
You gotta save Smokey!
What?
He's our enemy.
He can take care of himself.
No, he can't.
He's got Devil Fruit
power, so he can't swim.
He'll drown if you don't help him.
For crying out loud, Luffy,
do I really have to do this?
Oh, jeez.
All I did was follow my
captain's orders, that's it.
So, wouldn't read too much
into it if I were you.
It was one of his crazy
whims, pay it no mind.
Then you wouldn't have any gripes with me
carrying out my duties and arresting you,
right?
See, I knew this was a bad idea.
This is what you get for saving a marine.
They're here?
The Straw Hat Pirates? Yes, sir.
And it looks like they have
Captain Smoker surrounded.
Not for long, they won't. No way!
Yeah!
All right!
Full speed ahead to Alubarna!
There's Crocodile!
Let me at him!
Finally awake, huh?
You want some of this? Bring it on!
It's Smoker!
Luffy, forget it.
Let's just get out of here.
Come on!
I should, but you just saved my life.
This way! Hurry!
Go.
This is the only time I'm
letting you Straw Hats off.
Got it?
When we next meet, it's
going to be his enemies.
There they are!
Get them!
Reinforcements have
arrived, Captain Smoker!
Hold on!
Don't let them escape! Cut them off!
Well, that's our cue.
So, Vivi, which way to Alubarna? That way!
Due east across the
desert! They're running!
After them!
Luffy, come on.
What are you doing?
Aren't you coming?
Yeah.
They won't escape us, men!
Hey!
You're not such a bad guy, Smokey!
Would you get the hell out of here, Frye!
Don't worry, Captain Smoker!
We won't let those pirates get away!
I see them!
After them!
Captain, aren't you coming?
You go.
I'm tired. You're tired? Listen. Sir.
There's no point pursuing them now.
Have the men call off the chase.
I want everyone assembled here.
And contact headquarters.
Tell them to mobilize every military
vessel in the vicinity and route them here.
I want Alabasta surrounded.
You're calling for reinforcements, sir?
But, sir,
if I may point out,
our superiors may not
be willing to move that
many ships against such a
small number of pirates.
And since when do I care what
the superiors might think?
Sorry, sir.
I'll get right on it.
Hey!
The pursuit has been
called off! Come back!
Hurry!
Yeah, this way.
The scent of Nami's perfume is
getting stronger and stronger.
Hey!
Please tell me you guys aren't planning
to run all the way to Alubarna!
We've got eyelash!
Just where the hell is
that stupid camel anyway?
Close, I hope.
Doesn't this town have a stable?
Let's get some horses!
But the whole town is crawling
with marines! Not to worry.
Look ahead.
Hey guys, come on!
A crab.
Jumper, that's a moving crab.
Jumby.
Wow, awesome!
I can't believe my eyes.?
I bet it's delicious! I'll abide!
We get to ride it!
Pleased to meet ya!
Is it just me or does its
face look kind of shady?
Who cares?
At least we have a ride.
Say hello.
He's Eyelash's friend.
Eyelash has lots of friends in this
area because it's his hometown.
He was born and raised here.
He's nice, but kind of pervy.
I can't believe you found one.
Moving crabs are always
submerged under the sand,
so it's nearly impossible to spot one.
Judging by his size, I'd
say this guy's pretty fast.
Okay, time to move out.
Hang on, everyone.
Here we go!
Chopper, stop the crab!
It's him!
Hey, Luffy!
That damn idiot!
Luffy, no!
You guys go on ahead!
Don't worry about me!
Make sure you deliver Vivi home!
Safe and sound, you have to promise me!
Good luck, you guys.
Idiot.
Hey, let's go, Chopper.
Just keep going to
Alibar now. Right. Okay.
Let's go, crab!
Hey, hold on!
Wait, Zoro! No!
That's cold! Stop the crab!
We gotta go back!
It's all right, Vivi.
He'll be fine.
You have to trust me on this, okay?
I certainly feel sorry for the other guy.
Luffy shows no mercy to his prey.
And there's not a single person he's
gone after that was able to walk away.
Crocodile will fail.
Luffy will win.
It's that simple.
The moment that the Rebel Army started
running, this land's final hour was set.
Once the Royal Army and the
Rebel Army meet, this country,
the Kingdom of Alabasta,
will be gone forever.
If you truly are the one and only
hope for preventing that tragedy,
then you must survive, no matter what.
So, from this moment forward,
what happens to Luffy, or any of us for
that matter, isn't the least bit important.
But...
Vivi, this is a fight that
you and you alone started.
You're the one who bravely left
this land years ago and made
the decision to stand up against
a corrupt and evil organization.
However, don't make the mistake
of thinking you're alone anymore.
Yeah, that's right! Don't worry!
Because, because Captain
Usopp is going to protect you!
Luffy!
Listen!
We'll be waiting for you!
We'll be in our moment!
Yeah!
You could say Princess Vivi
slipped through our fingers.
No matter, the agents are still
scheduled to gather in Alubarna.
Contact them at once.
Strawhat, I'd say you've taken
this nonsense a little too far.
Nonsense.
Vivi doesn't see it that way.
You see, unlike most people, she
genuinely cares about others.
I guess deep down she's an optimist.
Even if it's not too realistic.
Take this revolt, for example.
She believes no one needs to die.
Nobody needs to die.
The problem with idealistic fools
like Princess Vivi is they take a
stand without any comprehension of
what is truly involved in a real fight.
Wouldn't you agree?
Yep.
But that doesn't change the fact
that as long as you're around,
Vivi's gonna fight until she
either wins or dies trying.
So I figure, I'll take
you down right here!
Such a foolish boy.
Despite what the idealists cry
about, there's one constant truth.
On the rough battlefields of
life, you either kill or die.
That's why I'm more than happy to shoot a
bullet through every
bleeding heart I meet.
Yeah, which proves you're
the bigger fool here.
you think something's funny?
perhaps you'd like to die as well?
nico robin if you want
to try go right ahead and
didn't you promise not
to call me by that name?
where are you going?
i'm headed to Alubarna see you there?
damn woman i'll never figure her out.
i've got three minutes to spare.
after that?
i'm certain your time
will have run out as well.
it's your move, kid.
with pleasure.
Gum-Gum!
HIT GUM!
And Gum-Gum!
by now it should be quite
obvious but i'll warn you
you cannot defeat me this is
an exercise in Utility. Stop!
Get me!
Listen to my warning and take heed.
If you continue this senseless attack?
You will have accomplished nothing.
and wasted what little time you have left.
Good critics, you lousy old sandgator!
You're wasting your time, boy.
You bastard!
No matter how hard you
fight against the truth,
there's no way a rubber freak like
you could even hope to rival me.
I'm sorry, my fist interrupted you.
Now, what was that?
I've had my fill of your
pathetic fun and games.
Let's end this, now. Fun and games!
Trust me, I'm dead serious!
Jerk!
Dammit, he's right, though.
He's got an answer for all of my attacks.
What do I do now?
We may both be pirates, but you
fall grossly short on skill.
Desert Spada!
Nice reflexes, boy.
A full-on hit from that
attack would have killed you.
What the?
That's one deep hole!
You may have Devil Fruit powers, but
you lack discipline and training.
With that, your skills could
be as formidable as any.
But you're not there yet.
Like so many fools, you waste time
obsessing over your abilities.
Gimmicks get you only so far in a fight
without the skill sets to back them up.
Desert Gyrosol!
What in the...?
What's going on?!
The sand!
It's sinking!
What is this?
What is this stuff? Let me out!
Let me out!
Let me out! What's wrong?
Never heard of quicksand?
It makes for a convenient
desert burial when
you need to get rid of someone in a hurry.
The sand is drawn down
into underground waterways,
and I have the good fortune of being
able to detect exactly where they are.
That advantage alone is enough to make me
unbeatable when fighting in the desert.
If you think I'm going to let myself
be buried alive in this sand trap,
you've got another thing coming!
You bastard!
I'm gone!
If I can't flunk you, then
maybe I could catch you instead!
I'm gone, shit!
HAVEN'T YOU LEARNED
ANYTHING, MORON, PREDICTABLE?
Shut up, gum -
This is really getting old.
LET ME GO!
I'M FLORTING YOU!
CHRISTEN CUTLIN
MY...
MY ARM!
What did you do?
It's all shriveled up like a mummy!
You turned my arm into a mummy!
Stop whining.
This is the price you pay.
The sand has absorbed all
the moisture from your arm.
You're lucky.
All I decided to attack was your arm.
I can do this all day long,
until you're a pile of dust.
You gotta be kidding me!
That's it! Water!
All in vain.
You're wrong, Sandy!
You see, that old guy in Yuba
gave me this barrel of water.
He spent all night
digging it up just for me!
Luffy, here, take this with you.
He's not scared and neither am I!
I'm not about to give in to
the sand without a fight!
Gum-Gum!
This is getting ridiculous.
My spine!
Enough!
This fails now!
Vermin, it is time to die.
Both you and the accursed land of Yuba.
Your three minutes are up.
Like I said at the start, I don't have
time to fool around with you any longer.
Now, Sables!
Ah, the sand so soothing and dry.
Look out! Sandstorm!
Right ahead in the sky!
Take shelter!
Wait a minute!
No, it's not coming this way!
It's headed south!
Captain Smoker, look! Up there!
Vivi! What's wrong?
There's a giant storm
moving toward Rain Base!
It's Crocodile!
Luffy, no!
Listen carefully.
Can you hear it move?
In this land, the prevailing winds
always blow from north to south.
And so,
if this infantile sandstorm of mine
were to, say, catch one of these winds,
it would grow exponentially
until it became a monster.
And following its trajectory south,
where do you think it would strike?
Tell me!
Then Yuba.
No, not there!
Dammit, why the hell are
you doing this? Stop it!
Look, it started.
It's headed south.
That nice old man has nothing
to do with this, you hear me?
Stop it or I swear I'll
kill you, you bastard!
You leave that old man alone!
You cannot alter fate that sandstorm
is going to pick up strength.
And eventually it will become strong
enough that even I can't stop it.
I don't believe you! Liar.
Yuba is finished.
You don't end this now.
I will.
Did you really think you were my equal?
There have been any number of rookies
like you who've challenged me.
And you've all shared a common
trait, fatal ineptitude.
And in the end, the only thing you
are truly qualified for is death.